# ZACK MERRELL

DIGITAL ARTIST SANTA CRUZ, 95060, UNITED STATES (831)566-6437

## • DETAILS •

204 HEATH ST, SANTA CRUZ, 95060, United States (831)566-6437 zmerrell831@gmail.com

• LINKS •

My Online Portfolio

• SKILLS •

Digital Illustration using Adobe Creative Cloud Suite

HTML and CSS

Photography

3D Modeling

JavaScript Coding

Video Production

## HOBBIES

Skateboarding Soccer

## PROFILE

I want to bring my knowledge in the Adobe Creative Cloud Suite, as well as other programs ranging from coding in Atom to 3D models in Maya or Dimension, to the workplace and utilize my experience to achieve both my own goals, as well as the goals of my employers and coworkers in the workplace. I want to do everything possible to create.

### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### Freelance Art/Design

November 2014 — Present

- Designed and created multiple logos for start-up businesses and professional social media accounts
- Sold prints of personal projects made in the Adobe Creative Cloud Suite to multiple clients
- Designed a variety of posters, flyers, and social media posts for a wide variety of reasons; as well as clients

#### Sales Associate at Vans, San Jose

November 2018 — August 2020

- Helped numerous customers find the apparel that was right for them
- Inspired outfits for customers looking for a wardrobe overhaul
- Designed multiple custom pairs of shoes for customers looking for something more personal to them

#### Sign Installer/Shop Help at Northwest Signs, Santa Cruz

August 2020 — Present

- Hands on field installer for a variety of signs (Neon, LEDs, etc.) for husinesses
- Shop help in the building of letters and other sign parts (Ex. O'Neil Surf Shop)

# EDUCATION

## Digital Media, San Jose State University, San Jose

August 2017 — Present (Graduating Spring 2022)

- · Learning to create using a variety of software
- Expanding my skills in coding, digital illustration, design, photography and film

#### EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

## D1 Club Soccer at San Jose State University

August 2017 — Spring 2020

- Goalkeeper
- · Captain of the team

#### Nu Alpha Kappa Fraternity

February 2020 — May 2022

- Actively holding positions on the Executive Board
- Have created all of the design work (Flyers, Social Media posts, Flags, etc.) for those 2 years

# 25+ Hours of Community Service